<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/blogs/the-barbers-chair.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/blogs/the-barbers-chair"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/blogs/the-barbers-chair.atom"/>
  <title>Rocky Mountain Barber Wholesale Canada - The Barber&apos;s Chair</title>
  <updated>2019-10-01T15:35:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Rocky Mountain Barber Wholesale Canada</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/blogs/the-barbers-chair/meet-anthony-a-barber-making-money-in-his-shop-with-rocky-mountain-barber</id>
    <published>2019-10-01T15:35:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-09-29T09:58:37-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/blogs/the-barbers-chair/meet-anthony-a-barber-making-money-in-his-shop-with-rocky-mountain-barber"/>
    <title>Meet Anthony - A Barber Making Money in his Shop with Rocky Mountain Barber</title>
    <author>
      <name>Rocky Mountain Barber</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<blockquote>
<h5><em>"Customers have been begging for the products since I began using them."</em></h5>
</blockquote>
<p>Anthony Sideri from North Andover, Massachusetts, describes cutting hair as a “true passion”, but chat to him for more than a few minutes, and it’s clear: that’s not the only one. Anthony took up the craft after the birth of his second daughter, realizing he wanted to spend more time with his children.</p>
<p>“I love every second that I am at the shop,” he says, “and I’m lucky enough now to cut hair a five-minute walk from my home. The Main Street location allows me to be in the center of town – and makes visits from my daughters more frequent.”<br><br>And when he’s not in the shop or spending time with his family? You’ll find Anthony at schools, jails, and hospitals, giving talks on the dangers of drug addiction.<br><br>He would know: not long ago, Anthony hit rock bottom. What started out as a high school flirtation with prescription medications turned into something far more sinister, as he fell into a life of heroin abuse.<br><br>It all came to a head when he was arrested, after robbing a bank to feed his next fix – he spent almost two full years in prison, and vowed never to touch the stuff again. That was in 2007, and he’s been true to his word: this is his tenth year sober.<br><br>“I completed barber school almost ten years ago,” he says, “and a year ago I realized that I wanted to be much more present than my previous job allowed.”<br><br>The life change is paying off – clients love the way he attends to their specific requirements and prioritizes what will make them look and feel great. His in-store range of Rocky Mountain Barber’s all-natural, plant-based products is a hit, he says.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1742/3401/files/SHOP.png?v=1569958280" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<blockquote>
<p>“Customers have been begging for the products since I began using them. The Rocky Mountain Barber Texture Paste is a real favorite. I have older gentlemen and mothers of small children all interested in the products – they’ve won the hearts of many moms because of the natural, plant-based ingredients.” </p>
</blockquote>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/collections/texture-paste" title="Texture paste"><strong><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1742/3401/products/2018main_medium.jpg?v=1566856970" alt=""></strong></a></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong></strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong><a href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/collections/texture-paste" title="wholesale texture paste">Carry Rocky Mountain Barber Texture Paste In Your Barbershop, Salon or Retail Location</a></strong></div>
<p><br>Anthony knows life isn’t easy. It’s something you have to fight for, with an eye fixed on what keeps you healthy and happy.<br><br>What makes Anthony a great barber? Simple: he’s been to a dark place and emerged with a new love for what matters in life. This is a man you can trust.</p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1790/8153/files/Divider.jpg?v=1524532582" alt="divider"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/products/Cedar_Spice_Shower_Wash_900x900_medium.jpg?v=1554163054" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;">
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ready to Start Carrying Rocky Mountain Barber Products? Click Below To Get Started.</span></h3>
<div align="center"><button type="submit" class="btn btn--clear btn--large btn--blog uppercase addToCart"><a href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/pages/get-started" style="text-decoration: none;">Get Started</a></button></div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/blogs/the-barbers-chair/q-a-with-a-rocky-mountain-barber-retailer-the-junto-emporium</id>
    <published>2019-07-15T10:17:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-09-29T11:48:38-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/blogs/the-barbers-chair/q-a-with-a-rocky-mountain-barber-retailer-the-junto-emporium"/>
    <title>Q&amp;A With A Rocky Mountain Barber Retailer: The Junto Emporium</title>
    <author>
      <name>Rocky Mountain Barber</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<blockquote>
<h5><span>"We have restocked several times and our community has given rave reviews on all of the products."</span></h5>
<p>- <em>Kathleen Bernhardt, Owner, The Junto Emporium</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p><i><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1742/3401/files/kathy.png?v=1563198930" alt=""></i></p>
<p><em>Kathleen Bernhardt is the owner of the The Junto Emporium, a menswear boutique based in Frenchtown, New Jersey.</em></p>
<p><strong>Q: Tell us about the Junto Emporium!</strong></p>
<p>A: The Junto Emporium opened it’s doors in July, 2018. We are located in Frenchtown, NJ which is a lovely village nestled along the Delaware River. The Junto is a menswear boutique, carrying a combination of new, previously owned and vintage clothing and accessories. We also carry footwear, skincare, beard care and locally made items. We strive to offer our clientele products that speak to the masculine in everyone!</p>
<p><strong>Q: What has the customer reaction been like to your store since you opened?</strong></p>
<p>A: The<span> </span><span class="il">Junto</span><span> </span>Emporium has been warmly welcomed into the Frenchtown community and as we grow our inventory we also grow our imprint on the town!  We are the only “men’s “ store around and we have hosted a variety of events including two fashion shows (fall/winter and spring/summer), various workshops, “Meet the Artist” events and we have a podcast called “Guy Talk” in the works.  We are considering expanding in the future and hope to have a few hipster barbers in our midst!</p>
<p><strong>Q: You obviously carry men's grooming products, what else do you currently carry?</strong></p>
<p>We carry a wide range of Rocky Mountain Barber products, including shaving products, skin care, body washes, deodorant and lip balms.  We have restocked several times and our community has given rave reviews on all of the products.  We even have some ladies who regularly purchase RMBC products for their own use! </p>
<div></div>
<div></div>
<p><strong>Q: What trends are you seeing in men's grooming and fashion. Where do you see the trends heading in men's style/grooming? </strong></p>
<div dir="ltr">
<div dir="ltr">
<div></div>
</div>
</div>
<div><em></em></div>
<p>I do see a trend in men wanting personal hygiene products made of all natural ingredients. Men are also seeking out locally, sustainably and consciously crafted products.</p>
<p> </p>
<div>
<blockquote>
<h5>"We are proud to offer Rocky Mountain Barber Company products to our community!"</h5>
</blockquote>
<p><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1742/3401/files/junto.png?v=1563199146" alt=""></p>
<p><em>If you are ever in the New Jersey area, be sure to drop by the Junto Emporium, located at <a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/The+Junto+Emporium/@40.5261939,-75.0618219,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0xd306188361b9ac8b?sa=X&amp;ved=2ahUKEwiN9KG-jbfjAhUPHc0KHfVnB4oQ_BIwD3oECAoQCA" title="Junto Emporium">26 Bridge St, Frenchtown, NJ, 08825</a>.</em></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/manshiitte/" title="The Junto Emporium"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1742/3401/files/f_logo_RGB-Blue_58.png?v=1563199792" alt="" width="75" height="75"></a> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/manshiitte/" title="Junto Emporium">Follow The Junto Emporium on Facebook</a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em><a href="https://www.instagram.com/explore/locations/223478435187249/the-junto-emporium?hl=en" title="Junto Emporium"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1742/3401/files/IG_Glyph_Fill.png?v=1563199734" alt="" width="75" height="75"></a> </em></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/explore/locations/223478435187249/the-junto-emporium?hl=en" title="Insatagram">Follow The Junto Emporium on Instagram</a></p>
</div>
<div></div>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1790/8153/files/Divider.jpg?v=1524532582" alt="divider">Ready to Start Carrying Rocky Mountain Barber Products? Click Below To Get Started.</span></h3>
<div align="center"><button type="submit" class="btn btn--clear btn--large btn--blog uppercase addToCart"><a href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/pages/get-started" style="text-decoration: none;">Get Started</a></button></div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/blogs/the-barbers-chair/5-ways-to-increase-sales-in-your-barbershop</id>
    <published>2019-07-11T12:58:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-07-19T12:47:09-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/blogs/the-barbers-chair/5-ways-to-increase-sales-in-your-barbershop"/>
    <title>5 Ways to Increase Sales in your Barbershop</title>
    <author>
      <name>Rocky Mountain Barber</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Your barbershop is your mancave-- a sanctuary where guys can escape, groom and relax. But more importantly, this home-away-from-home is your business. No matter how much love and passion you invest in this place, sometimes you need to take a step back and think more like an entrepreneur. You might have the most talented barbers in the city, but without the right goal-setting plan, your business won’t scale. To help you raise the bar, we sat down with the most successful barbershop owners in Canada and asked for some valuable tips.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are five ways to  increase sales in your barbershop.</span></p>
<ol>
<li><b> Be smarter about internet marketing</b></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Every barbershop has room to grow. The only problem is that when you're stuck in your comfort zone  as a business-owner, you stick to the same stale marketing routines that feel safe instead of taking new risks. Just like what you’d tell clients who repeat their old hairstyle, it’s better to be current and fresh.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even if you update your website or use Facebook marketing, your sales won’t grow if there’s no strategy. These moves are only meaningful when you’re reaching your audience. Take this scenario, for example: you create a paid Facebook ad, targeting the cool urban millennial, but your shop is located in a suburb with lots of middle-aged dads. Here, you’re not being smart about internet marketing. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here’s something you could do instead: reach out to five local guys with a decent following on social media. Offer them a full grooming service (and maybe a free product) in exchange for promotion. They’ll post a photo on social media, showing off their dapper look, along with a link to your website and a recommendation for your services. Chances are that a few of their buddies will flock to your barbershop. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Always have a strategy and know your demographic. Being creative and calculated with your internet marketing is key. Ultimately, it doesn’t matter how much you use Instagram or make tweets if you’re not targeting your audience. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So channel your inner artist and consider how to be more inventive and meaningful with how you use social media. Don’t forget about platforms like Snapchat and Pinterest-- two very underused marketing opportunities. </span></p>
<ol start="2">
<li><b> Keep updating your skills</b></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/files/skills.png?v=1563554653" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Does your staff stay up-to-date with the latest grooming trends? When styles are constantly changing, clients prefer barbers who know how to perform the latest techniques. Even if your barbershop mainly caters to older gentlemen, these guys still appreciate the chance to look modern and handsome. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To offer this caliber of service, your staff need to stay current with their knowledge base and skills. That’s right-- back to class you go! Every six months or so, send two staff members to a training workshop. When they return, they’ll teach these new techniques to your other barbers. The luxury of having well-trained staff who are committed to professional growth is vital for attracting customers. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If there’s an overseas workshop being led by a world-renowned barber, try to seize this opportunity. Having your team trained by the best makes your barbershop the best.</span></p>
<ol start="3">
<li><b> Hire more barbers</b></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/files/barbers.png?v=1563554823" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As your customer base increases, you must hire more barbers. Yes, these updates will cost you money, but it’s all part of increasing your sales over the long-term. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You can expand your team gradually, making the process safer on your pocket. Perhaps at the beginning stage, you’ll hire one extra barber for just two days per week. Then, as the new recruit attracts more clients, you’ll increase their work schedule. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Do your best to support your most recent team member in growing their customer base. Your receptionist is a great place to start. When new customers call to schedule an appointment, have your receptionist endorse your new barber, helping to build their client roster. And if your budget is still raw, your new barber can double as an assistant until they gain more customers. </span></p>
<ol start="4">
<li><b> Extend store hours</b></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you can't increase your team, increase your hours. This move, although simple, can be one of the cleverest ways to increase sales in your barbershop. Why? Because on average, your competitors close by 5 pm on weekdays and even earlier on Sundays. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The downside to this schedule is that working clients have to coordinate their haircut with their lunch hour. This approach makes weekends the most popular day which jam-packs your schedule. If your barbershop is one of the rare few that’s opened until 9pm, that’s a huge incentive for customers. And if the late hours might worry the client’s wifey, you can always give out appointment cards to prove their alibi. </span></p>
<ol start="5">
<li><b> Carry the right products (i.e. Rocky Mountain Barber products)</b></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/files/pomade.png?v=1563554281" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A barbershop is only as professional as their products. When your shelves are stocked with top-of-the-line products, your customers will invest more trust in the quality of your overall service. Not only will you enhance the image of your barbershop, but you’ll also boost sales.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You can secretly promote the products by having your barbers use them on clients. It’s free advertising! So while the barber is applying pre-shave oil or lathering on the shaving cream, they should casually boast about the product’s unique qualities. The barber can follow up by asking the client which products they use. Many men stick to simple and accessible stuff, usually the average drugstore variety. By enticing them something more premium and handsome-smelling, you’ll see your sales rise.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To build the right product stock, do your research and network with other entrepreneurs who specialize in high quality grooming essentials. Choose a brand that focuses on pure ingredients to seperate yourself from the generic brands that overload the chemicals. Rocky Mountain Barber is a Canadian brand that lives and breathes natural grooming products. Even world class athletes like three-time Olympian Christopher Spring and Pro Boxer Joey Spencer are loyal to Rocky Mountain Barber products. Never underestimate the importance of health as a selling point.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Every business needs a plan for success. As long as you’ve got a clear vision, your barbershop will be that special haven, eventually attracting gents  outside your area code. Remember that being a successful entrepreneur is a lifelong learning curve. Good luck.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1790/8153/files/Divider.jpg?v=1524532582" alt="divider"></span></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ready to Start Carrying Rocky Mountain Barber Products? Click Below To Get Started.</span></h3>
<div align="center"><button type="submit" class="btn btn--clear btn--large btn--blog uppercase addToCart"><a href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/pages/get-started" style="text-decoration: none;">Get Started</a></button></div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/blogs/the-barbers-chair/what-products-should-i-sell-in-my-barbershop</id>
    <published>2019-06-19T14:35:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-07-17T08:39:20-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/blogs/the-barbers-chair/what-products-should-i-sell-in-my-barbershop"/>
    <title>What Products Should I Sell in My Barbershop?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Rocky Mountain Barber</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1742/3401/files/whatproduct.jpg?v=1486406892" alt="Wholesale-Barbershop-Products-Main">Guys aren’t great at grooming. Ask any experienced barber, accustomed to helping clean up the mess men make of themselves day in and day out, and he’ll tell you: looking after their appearance is just not something that comes naturally to most guys.</p>
<p>This is why a barber is such an important figure in a man’s life. Sure, most of the time he might be content with the odd shampoo or cursory shave, but put a job interview or first date in front of him, and suddenly, he’ll make it your job to undo days or even weeks of personal neglect.</p>
<p>And when that day comes, you need to be ready. We’re talking battle-ready, with every possible weapon of mess-destruction in your utility belt, prepared to wage war against dry and damaged hair, tangled beards, furry necks, lengthy sideburns, unkempt eyebrows, and even untrimmed, untidy forests of ear hair.</p>
<p>Yup, men aren’t great at grooming – which is why they look to you, their barber, as a miracle worker, armed with rare skills, expert insights and years of diligent training, ready and waiting to get them looking great, and feeling even better, in no time at all.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1742/3401/files/Wholesale-Mens-Grooming-Products.jpg?v=1486407183" alt="Men's-Grooming-Wholesale-Products"></p>
<p>Your secret weapon: the right products. Knowing which hair and beard grooming products work best, and why, will keep your customers coming back for more.</p>
<p>Take a look around and ask, What products should I sell in my barbershop? Do you have what it takes to turn cavemen into cultured gents? Here’s how to ensure you meet their exacting expectations, every time.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/pages/request-samples" target="_blank" title="FREE Sample" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1742/3401/files/click23.jpg?v=1489786884" alt="free barber samples"></a></p>
<p> <strong>5 Essential Items You Should Sell in Your Barbershop</strong></p>
<p>What’s the one reason most men ignore their grooming needs? It’s not because they can’t see what’s wrong, as they know their bodies better than anyone, and it’s not because they simply don’t care, as you know when they run to your shop for help. No, it’s because they don’t have the tools.</p>
<p>Give a guy a jar of pomade or eyedropper of beard oil to go what that new look, and chances are he’ll ask, What’s this for? His cluelessness is your cue: stock up on the best products, explain what they do and show them how well they work, and you’ll be doing a public service.</p>
<p>So what products should you sell in your barbershop or salon? Let’s take a look at the hair and beard savers most guys don’t know a thing about.</p>
<h2>1. Pomade </h2>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/products/Pomade_900x900_medium.jpg?v=1554163182" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/products/Pomade-Main-2018_d5a65c1c-41cb-4b90-98c5-341afd0f4789_medium.jpg?v=1561484067" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>A quality pomade will help replicate the effect of great-looking, just-been-cut hair every day. Look for a water-based product that can be washed out with damaging the follicles, while offering high shine and a firm hold.</p>
<h2>2. Texture Paste</h2>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img alt="" src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/products/2018main_24f8f357-6040-4d23-9de5-08fad170220b_medium.jpg?v=1561484079" style="float: none; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/products/Hair_Texture_Paste_900x900_medium.jpg?v=1554163315" alt=""></p>
<p>Any great look will deteriorate through the day – but gel or hair cream will only make this problem worse, leading to clumping and flaking. A plant-based paste, with ingredients like beeswax, lanolin and glycerin, will solve both issues at once, helping to maintain a natural, healthy flexibility and style.</p>
<h2>3. Beard Balm</h2>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/products/Main-Beard-Balm_medium.jpg?v=1560773628" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Guys love beards because, supposedly, they don’t take much work – and this is how they end up with dry and tangled whiskers that are impossible to control. Help them out by pointing out a good, all-natural beard oil: think ingredients like essential oils, beeswax and shea butter, and scent that brings back memories of the mountains.</p>
<h2>4. Beard Oil</h2>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/products/Main-2018-900_900x_70cae845-a9eb-4625-8bc2-58b7301efcc2_medium.jpg?v=1560773622" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>The number one mistake men make when growing out a poorly maintained beard: shaving it off. And you can understand why: a dry and scruffy beard can itch like crazy. The right oil will keep the area hydrated and make sure the follicles are well-fed, eliminating the irritation. </p>
<h2>5. All-In-One Shower Wash</h2>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img alt="" src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/products/Rocky_Mountain_Barber_Company_Cedar_Spice_Shower_Wash_98c6f579-50fd-4664-a1f0-6c456070939a_medium.jpg?v=1561401059" style="float: none; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p><span>Our all-in-one wash will provide you will a consistent sensory profile so you'll never have to worry about inconsistent performance again.</span><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1790/8153/files/Divider.jpg?v=1524532582" alt="divider"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0091/1913/7888/products/Cedar_Spice_Shower_Wash_900x900_medium.jpg?v=1554163054" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ready to Start Carrying Rocky Mountain Barber Products? Click Below To Get Started.</span></h3>
<div align="center"><button type="submit" class="btn btn--clear btn--large btn--blog uppercase addToCart"><a href="https://rockymountainbarberwholesale.ca/pages/get-started" style="text-decoration: none;">Get Started</a></button></div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
